https://www.listrak.com/privacy-and-terms/privacy-policy

SolutionsCross Channel OrchestrationCreate data-driven, intelligent journeys across channels.Customer InsightsUnify customer data for instant insights, exploration and activation.Behavioral Based TriggersAutomate abandonment campaigns, product alerts, loyalty and more.Unified 360° Customer ProfileCapture critical customer signals across the customer journey.Predictive PersonalizationHarness historical data to increase results across every campaign.Growth Xcelerator PlatformIntegrated identity resolution that increases conversion rates.ChannelsEmailSophisticated enterprise email marketing tools for retailers.SMS/MMSEngage customers on their mobile device with text messages.SocialConvert highly-targeted customers with social campaign audiences.Mobile PushCreate and manage iOS or Android app mobile push messages.WebBoost on-site conversions by personalizing each site visit.Direct MailPower offline direct mail campaigns with targeted segmentation.ClientsFeatured ClientsJoin 1,000+ retailers that trust Listrak for their marketing automation. Success StoriesStories from retailers that have delivered results with ListrakIndustry Leading NPSWe're proud to deliver exceptional value for our clients.CompanyWhy Listrak?Listrak delivers seamless, personalized cross-channel interactions — all from one integrated platform.News & EventsGet the latest Listrak news and event information.LeadershipThe Listrak Executive Management TeamCareersLife at Listrak.  Join our Team!ContactWe're available anytime, 24/7, every day of the yearLearnRevenue Gap IndexBlogWhite PapersDevelopersRecent PostsEventListrak Private Virtual Event: Bobby Flay Private Interactive Cooking ClassEventListrak Private Virtual Event: Silver Oak Wine TastingListrak hosted more than 80 retailers and brands from across the country during private Silver Oak wine tasting virtual events live from their tasting room in Napa Valley. PartnersEcommerce Platform IntegrationsLearn about ecommerce platforms that integrate with ListrakTechnology PartnersFind a trusted Technology Provider PartnerAgency PartnersGain marketing expertise and assistance from Agency Partners.UPS Alliance PartnersAn exclusive partnership to help businesses drive revenue growth.Become a PartnerPartner relationships play a significant and valuable role in our success and the success of our mutual clients.Get StartedLoginListrak's Privacy PolicyHomeContactEffective Date: January 1, 2020This Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy” or “Policy”) describes how Listrak Inc. (“Listrak”, “we”, “our”, or “us”) collects and uses personal information of users of this website, www.listrak.com (the “Site”), and users of Listrak’s Services Platform (the “Platform” and the services provided on the Platform, collectively, the “Services”). This Privacy Policy also describes your choices regarding use, access and correction of your personal information. The use of information collected through our Platform shall be limited to the purpose of providing the Services for which our clients have engaged Listrak. We periodically update this Privacy Policy and reserve the right to change the provisions of this Policy or our privacy practices at any time. If you are a user of Listrak’s Platform, then you will receive notice when this Privacy Policy is modified. If not, then we encourage you to review this Site periodically and we will alert you that changes have been made by updating the Effective Date of this Policy. Your use of the Site or the Platform constitutes consent to any changes in this Policy as in effect on the date of such use.Your Rights to Access Your Personal InformationYou have the right to access personal information about you that Listrak has collected through this Site by sending a request for access to privacy@listrak.com or calling our toll-free number 877-362-4556. You can also request that we correct or delete any such information by using the same methods. To verify that the request is authentic, we will match the identifying information provided by the requestor to the personal information of the requester already maintained. For example, we may require that the requester send such request from the email address associated with the personal information. While we will comply reasonably and respond to your request within the timeframe required by applicable law, we may need to retain some of your information for our own record keeping or to fulfill a legal obligation. You will not receive discriminatory treatment should you decide to exercise any rights set forth in this Policy.Listrak’s clients use our Platform to contact consumers. If your information was collected by one of Listrak’s clients or some other third party, you must contact that party with any questions or concerns about its use of your personal information. That party’s privacy practices may differ from those of Listrak. This Policy is not intended to supersede or govern the privacy policies and practices of Listrak’s clients or any other third party.Listrak, as a Service Provider, collects information under the direction of our clients and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal information may be processed as part of providing our Services. Any requests that Listrak receives while acting as a Service Provider will be denied and the consumer will be directed to submit the request directly to the Listrak client. Listrak may transfer personal information to vendors that help us provide Services. Access to your personal information by these vendors is limited to the information reasonably necessary for the vendor to perform its limited function for us. These vendors must abide by our data privacy and security requirements and are not permitted to use your personal information for any other purpose. Representative business processes that our vendors assist us with include:Cybersecurity monitoring and intrusion detectionPayment processingWebsite analyticsCloud infrastructureContent delivery Listrak clients may log into the Listrak Platform to correct, update, or delete their personal information by making the change on the user account settings page, or by emailing our Client Support Team at support@listrak.com.Opting OutIf you subscribe to our email newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send our marketing/update emails to you. You may choose to stop receiving our marketing/update emails by following the unsubscribe instructions in those emails, or you can contact us at privacy@listrak.com.What is personal information?Personal information means information that specifically identifies an individual person, such as name, mailing address, email address, phone number, or account number. It may also include other information about you, such as gender, date of birth, or other demographic information, or about your use of the Site, such as IP address or cookies, if that other information is linked to your personal information.How your information is collectedListrak collects personal information that you provide to us. For example:If you sign up for Listrak’s Services or request a demo, Listrak may require you to register by providing your name, email address, phone number, and other information. You may be asked to create a username and password to login to our Platform.If you apply for a job with Listrak, we may ask you to provide more detailed and sensitive personal information required for compliance with our hiring and equal opportunity policies and practices.Our Site includes social media features, such as links to our Facebook, YouTube, LinkedIn, and Twitter pages. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.Our Site also includes client testimonials and publicly accessible blogs or community forums where you may post information, or we may post information with your consent.We also collect some of your information automatically when you visit this Site or log on to the Platform. For example, this Site collects your Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, the files viewed on our Site (e.g. HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data and records the pages that you visit and other information about your activity on the Site.Like many other websites, we ask you to allow us to use “cookies” to remember information about you and improve your browsing experience on our Site. If you reject cookies, you may still use our Site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our Site may be limited. We may also work with third-party providers who may use cookies on our Site. You can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. For more information about cookies, including how to set your internet browser to reject cookies, please go to https://www.allaboutcookies.org or https://www.networkadvertising.org. If you are located in the European Union, please go to https://www.youronlinechoices.eu. Please note that you will continue to receive generic ads.We also may receive your information from another party that has collected it from you, such as our clients or your employer, so that we can contact you or so that you can access our Services in furtherance of their business. Their collection of your information is governed by their own privacy policies. If you believe that we received your personal information and you would like to request that it be removed from our database, please contact us at privacy@listrak.com.What we do with your informationListrak may use your personal information to:provide Services;send requested information on Services or otherwise respond to questions, concerns, and client support inquiries;send marketing communications;create demographic profiles of our clients and visitors to target our email alerts and website marketing;improve the Services we offer you or the functionality of our Site;identify and evaluate applicants for potential employment;comply with applicable employment laws and provide employee benefits and services.Listrak does not sell or disclose personal information to third parties and does not transfer or share consumers’ personal information between its clients. Listrak will share your personal information only:with your consent;to fulfill a legal obligation, including:in response to lawful requests or legal process, including in response to law enforcement requirements; oras part of a business transaction, sale or transfer, or bankruptcy proceedingfor protection of personal or public safety or to prevent illegal activities;to protect our own rights including enforcing our own policies, contracts, and terms of use.Listrak may also use personal information for internal purposes, such as to monitor the performance of its Platform, or to track the effectiveness of and improve its Services. Listrak may also share aggregate, deidentified, or pseudonymous data with third parties.How Listrak Protects Personal InformationListrak follows generally accepted standards to protect personal information and information submitted by our clients, both during transmission and once we receive it. Listrak maintains all information in carrier-class secure facilities protected by firewalls and other security devices. These measures are designed to protect information from loss, misuse, or unauthorized alteration. Listrak employs various information security mechanisms and internal policies and procedures to protect information from disclosure to unauthorized third parties. Listrak routinely audits its practices and policies to meet industry standards for data protection. Listrak provides an encrypted, password-protected mechanism for logging in, viewing, uploading, and extracting client data on our Platform.Personal information provided to Listrak by its clients remains the property of its clients. If you have any questions about the security of your personal information, you can contact us at privacy@listrak.com.Privacy Shield RequirementsListrak complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it will abide by the Privacy Shield Principles regarding personal information transferred from any of Listrak’s clients in the European Union and Switzerland to Listrak in the United States.Listrak is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission.If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov.In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Listrak commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your information. Individuals in the European Union with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Policy should first contact Listrak at privacy@listrak.com.Listrak will respond to your inquiry or complaint within 45 days. If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request. This third-party dispute resolution program is specifically designed to resolve Privacy Shield-related complaints with no cost to you. If neither Listrak nor our third-party dispute resolution provider resolves your complaint, you may pursue binding arbitration through the Privacy Shield Panel as described in the Privacy Shield Agreement, Annex I, to be created jointly by the US Department of commerce and the European Commission.EU and Swiss residents have rights to access personal data about them, and to limit use and disclosure of their personal data. With our Privacy Shield certification, Listrak has committed to respect those rights. Because Listrak personnel have limited ability to access data our clients submit to our Services, if you wish to request access, to limit use, or to limit disclosure, please provide the name of the Listrak client who submitted your data to our Services. We will refer your request to that client and will support the client as needed in responding to your request. Listrak acknowledges potential liability in cases of onward transfer of personal data to third parties who do not meet the criteria as set forth in this Policy. Listrak complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU, including the onward transfer liability provisions.Listrak uses an annual self-assessment to review its compliance with this Policy. Any employee who Listrak determines has violated this Policy will be subject to discipline, up to and including termination of employment.Who to ContactTo report any issues or concerns, or to contact Listrak with any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, email us at privacy@listrak.com, or call 877-362-4556.You may also contact us as follows:Fax: 717-627-8001Postal Address: Listrak, 100 West Millport Road, Lititz, PA 17543Thank you! Your submission has been received!Oops! Something went wrong while submitting the form.SolutionsCross Channel OrchestrationBehavioral Based TriggersPredictive PersonalizationCustomer InsightsUnified 360° Customer ProfileGrowth Xcelerator PlatformChannelEmailSocialWebSMS/MMSMobile PushDirect MailClientsFeatured ClientsSuccess StoriesIndustry Leading NPSCompanyNews and EventsLeadershipCareersContactLearnBlogWhite PapersDevelopersPartnersOur PartnersBecome a partnerPrivacy PolicyAcceptable Use PolicyCopyright NotificationSecurity Policy©2020 ListrakAll rights reservedAffiliations and acknowledgements
